# **ANGAD SINGH**

#### **CONTACT INFO**

- +1289-946-3260
- angadpreetmalhi@gmail.com
- AVancouver, British Columbia
- https://angadpreetsingh.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ angadpreetmalhi

#### **SKILLS**

- Python
- JavaScript, React
- HTML CSS SASS
- Django/Flask
- APIs
- Git & GitHub
- MySQL
- Jenkins/Docker
- Bootstrap
- WordPress
- Office 365
- Networking Skills
- Technical Skills
- Software Testing
- Troubleshooting
- Windows/Mac/Linux
- Document & Reporting
- Financial Record Keeping
- MS Word/Excel/PowerPoint
- Management Skills
- Leadership
- Customer Service

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- DEVOPS ComIT
- Python, GitHub, Jenkins, Docker, Deployment, Pipelines
- Networking, Virtualization, Operating Systems
- > SQL FOR DATA SCIENCE IBM
- Frontend Fundamentals HTML & CSS PIRPLE.COM

## **PROFILE**

Full Stack Developer with experience in the following programming languages: Python, JavaScript, React, SQL, .Net, Java and expertise with HTML and CSS seeks to establish a career as the Full Stack Developer. I am very familiar and experienced with CMS and frameworks such as Django, Flask, WordPress, Bootstrap

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Computer System Technician-Software Support Diploma**

Mohawk College Hamilton Ontario | 2015 - 2017

- Web languages including HTML, JavaScript, and .NET
- Programming languages including Python, Java, MySQL
- Tools and frameworks including IntelliJ, Visual Studio, PyCharm, NetBeans and MVC

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **Technology Consultant**

Staples Canada Richmond British Columbia | 2019 - 2020

- Assist clients with product knowledge and technical questions.
- Troubleshooting technical issues, Installing, and configuring software.
- Writing reports on the status of all hardware and software.
- Setup Computers, Printers, Routers and Scanners. and MVC

#### **Assistant Manager**

Friendship Foods Company, Vancouver British Columbia | 2017 - 2019

- Managed a team of supervisors and over 18 staff members.
- Handling customer inquiries and complaints.
- Exceeded sales goals and accomplished business objectives by inspiring staff and promoting target products.
- Managed inventory control processes, schedules, and delegating assignments to meet coverage and service demands.

#### **PROJECTS**

- Personal Website: http://angadpreetsingh.com
  HTML, CSS, SASS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP
- Weather App: http://angadwapp.pythonanywhere.com
  Python, Django, APIs, SQLite 3, Tailwinds
- Note Maker: https://angadpreetmalhi.github.io/noteMaker
  HTML & CSS, JavaScript
- BC PNP Calculator: https://angadpreetmalhi.github.io/bcPnpCalculators
  HTML & CSS, SASS, JAVASCRIPT
- List Maker: http://angadpreetmalhi.pythonanywhere.com
  Python, Django, Bootstrap, JavaScript
- React Js TodoAPP: https://angadpreetmalhi.github.io/todoApp
- React Js Netflix App: https://angadpreetmalhi.github.io/react-netflix-app